DANIEL FLORES GUERRERO

Junior Software Developer

1874 Rue Saint-Clement Montreal, QC H1V3E6 (514)-730-7996

Software developer with more than one-year of experience working with Java web-based and SOA applications. Full stack Java developer devoted to the user experience as means of the entire application. Disciplined student and passionate professional looking to join the best development team.

<u>daniellesifg@gmail.com</u> - <u>www.gitlab.com/Danielifg</u> - <u>www.github.com/Danielifg</u> - <u>www.linkedin.com/in/Danielifg</u> www.danielfg.com

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- **CLIENT SIDE:** JSF Primefaces, Bootfaces ,PrimeNG, RichFaces themes & components, Ajax, ES6, jQuery, ReactJs, Bootstrap, Zurb Foundation.
- **SERVER SIDE**: Java SE 8, Java EE 6,RESTful and SOAP services, JDBC, Hibernate, MySQL Server, Glassfish Server, Maven Python3, Flask web framework, Python open computer vision, Python moviepy library, Amazon EC2 instance, Docker, JUnit and Selenium browser automation.
- OPERATING SYSTEMS: Unix, Windows 10 Pro, Linux Debian, Ubuntu Server.

EXPERIENCE

FiloWifi Solutions Inc. MTL ,QC.

2017-06 to 2018-02

Software Developer

Project 1: Social Login website for WiFi hotspot, Atlantic city, NJ, USA.

- Successfully deployed a login and management portal for user data from free wifi network, Atlantic City, NJ beach seven mile boardwalk.
- Achieved a 30% increase of users during the first two weeks of deployment via marketing promotions on the site.

Project 2: Emergency Messaging System, Atlantic city, NJ, USA.

• Collaborated with local police department providing a browser interface to beach boardwalk LED screens for emergency messages. Duration: six months.

Project 3: People Counting Application, Atlantic city, NJ, USA.

- Developed command line program to count people on video surveillance records.
- Created statistics of people looking at advertisements for marketing purposes.

Project 4: Ubuntu Linux Server Setup for testing networking hardware.

 Managed Kernel Based Virtual Machine infrastructure to host Wireless LAN controllers and simple network management protocol (SNMP) servers.

AXDEV Group Inc. MTL QC.

2015-01 to 2015-06

Project Manager Assistant.

- Migrated PDF internal database to relational database server.
- Optimized DB user experience with Java web-based application.

EDUCATION

*	Udacity Web Platform. ReactJs NanoDegree.	2017-12 to present
*	Concordia University. Diploma in Java Application Development.	2016-06 to 2017-06
*	McGill University. International Exchange co-op program.	2015-01 to 2015-06
*	Monterrey Institute of Technology and Higher Education. Mexico.	
	B.A. in International commerce.	2010-05 to 2015-12
*	Languages: English, French, Spanish.	